tf2wh.com 2016-05-16

# Norganna's AddOns

This is Norganna's AddOns Pty Ltd Online Privacy Policy. It is our corporate policy and generically applies to all sites operated and controlled by our company.

## What information do we collect?

  * We collect information from you when you register on our sites, place an order, fill out a form or submit posts to our forum.
  * When ordering or registering on our sites, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, username or date of birth.
  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
  * We may use cookies, beacons, tracking pixels or other tracking technology for the purpose of delivering targeted advertising and/or content to you.

Other information collected for specific websites:

**TF2 Warehouse (TF2WH) - http://www.tf2wh.com**

**DOTA2 Auction House (DOTA2AH) - http://www.dota2ah.com**

The TF2WH and DOTA2AH websites make use of certain non-public end user data acquired through the Steam API which contains your TF2 and DOTA2 inventory / armory contents. This call is made whenever you visit the consignment page on the TF2WH or manage page on DOTA2AH, and will only succeed if you have your Steam profile set to public. The retrieved data will be stored on our servers in the United States of America, for a maximum duration of 60 minutes as part of a cache system designed to reduce load on the Steam Servers, and increase TF2WH and DOTA2AH site responsiveness. The retrieved data will not be disclosed to third parties and is only viewable by you after you have authenticated successfully to TF2WH and DOTA2AH via the "Sign in through Steam" Steam OpenID provider. 

**SteamPrepaid.com - http://steamprepaid.com**

The details captured during registration are protected by security safeguards as detailed in this Privacy Policy. The personal information collected as part of your registration is collected to enable identification of prize recipients and for future marketing and promotional purposes.

## What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalise your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs).
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you).
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs).
  * To process transactions. 

> Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

  * To administer a contest, giveaway, promotion, survey or other site feature.
  * To send periodic emails. 

> The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

## How do we protect your financial information?

We utilise the services of a third party billing provider. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorised with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

## Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders by contacting customer service.

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

## Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our websites and not to information collected offline.

## Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our [Online Privacy Policy](http://norganna.com/privacy.php).

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on **Monday 2 June, 2014**.

Any enquires please email: **staff at norganna.com**
